/* This file is pending for deletion. The issues management please visit: http://cubeexercise.codeplex.com/WorkItem/List.aspx */

3. 研究Client Profile(Beta?)
4. 加一个检测.NET是否安装的stub(1.0.122.0)
5. 公式分组（熊熊、大板）(1.1.206.0)
6. 每个用户分别记录成绩，成绩与配置/设置文件分离
Save the time consumed by user to perform every algorithm.
CubeExercise should be able to save the time of each formula performed by user. And then it's easy to calculate the best, average and the standard deviation.
7. 在“随机练习”中显示魔方当前公式完成后正确的状态，方便做完每个公式之后实时比较
Real Time Comparison
During the "Random Exercise" tab, the user have to switch to "Simulator" tab and compare the cube status. CubeExercise should be able to show the real time status in the "Random Exercise" tab. So the user is able to compare the cube with the current correct status after he performed every formula.

8. 支持视频
Video Demo Support
When a user is learning and practising a new algorithm, he should be able to view the finger demo for every formula.

9. 软件自动检查更新
Check the newer version automatically
CubeExercise should be able to check whether there's a newer version. This relies on a web site.

10.3D立体魔方模型
3D Cube Model
CubeExercise should have a 3D cube model. It's better to be a SilverLight control which can be used on a web page directly.

11.生成并在内存中保存公式的转换矩阵及逆矩阵（用来产生用此公式可以还原的case），以便做其他计算
Generate the cube transform matrix for every algorithm.
Now CubeExercise has one transform matrix for every single action (such as R, L, F'...). This could improve the performance and can be used to generate the case for the algorithm dynamically.

12.自定义公式集合，允许每个人定义多个公式集合
Active Algorithm Set for everyone

14.根据现有的公式集合动态生成公式循环列表
Generate the algorithms circling table for a specific algorithms set dynamically.
It's helpful to learn a set of algorithms since its easy to setup up any algorithm.


16.允许使用多个公式文件，新增公式的时候只需要增加文件就可以了。
Multiple Alrorithm Files Support
When the user needs to add more alrigithms, he only needs to download a new XML file and copy it to the application direction.

17.公式文件中将公式定义和分组定义分离，允许一个公式在不同的分组组中出现多次，但是保证在练习的时候同一个公式只出现一次。
Separate the Algorithm Definition and Grouping Definition
So one algorithm can occur in different groups and the same algorithm in different groups can be identified when exercising.

18.增加打乱及计时、统计功能（参照CCT）
Add a Scrambler and Timer
That is, all the functionalities implemented by CCT.
